35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
35 millimeter slides
2.1.5.1
Marist College
  More
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  Box 1589
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 27 (continued from previous box) [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University accompany this slide presentation, 1975; 1 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Three people talking together], 1
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Close-up of hands being held], 2
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Two girls working on sculptures], 3
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: A building], 4
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People perfomring the Eucharist], 5
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Group of people sitting on couches, having a discussion], 6
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Prayer Tower], 7
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: (Blank photo)], 8
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People working on ceramics], 9
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Men working on roof], 10
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man and woman talking together], 11
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man helping a boy play the guitar], 12
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Men working on a project], 13
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People giving a performance on stage], 14
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Group of people sitting on couches, talking], 15
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Women on stage, singing], 16
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People giving a performance on stage], 17
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People giving a performance on stage], 18
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People giving a performance on stage], 19
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People giving a performance on stage], 20
  - Carousel number 27 (continued from previous box) [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University accompany this slide presentation, 1975; 2 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man with microphone talking to woman], 1
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Group of people together, smiling], 2
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man with guitar, singing], 3
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man with microphone], 4
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman singing (?)], 5
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man with microphone], 6
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man and woman together singing a duet], 7
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man sitting and talking], 8
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man talking to girls], 9
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: A construction site], 10
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: A building], 11
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Crowd of people], 12
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Crowd of people holding hands, praying], 13
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man talking with students outside], 14
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People giving a performance], 15
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man and woman sitting in a library, reading a book together], 16
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man and woman working on a project], 17
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Two men working on an experiment], 18
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Tow girls reading together], 19
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man handing a diploma at graduation ceremony], 20
  - Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation], circa 1973; 3 (Box 1589)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation] [: Lowell Thomas with T.E. Lawrence in Arabia], 1
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Family portrait of Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 2
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas standing with a man in uniform], 3
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of land], 4
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Drawing of large building with a fountain in front of it], 5
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: A [house (?)] barn], 6
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: People mounted on horses in front of [house (?)] barn], 7
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Plaque in a rock (illegible) [Oblong Meeting House]], 8
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas leading a horse out of a stable], 9
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas on a bucking horse], 10
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Waterfall], 11
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of land], 12
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Close-up of Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Jr. and another man], 13
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas talking with Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 14
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas standing on steps with another man], 15
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas talking with Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 16
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Group of men together for a photo, Lowell Thomas in back row to right], 17
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas with a group of men sitting in a car], 18
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: A band playing and people dancing], 19
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas with little boy on fallen tree? over the lake], 20
  - Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation], circa 1973; 4 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Man mounted on horse looking at a house], 1
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: House], 2
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas sitting in a row boat, reading a newspaper], 3
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of the back of a white house], 4
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: A white house hidden behind pine trees], 5
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of land], 6
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Road lined with trees], 7
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Man on skiis looking at house], 8
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Cherry trees on roadside], 9
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: People on golf course], 10
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: House hidden behind tree], 11
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Road], 12
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas and their dog in a golf cart], 13
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Road], 14
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of the back of house], 15
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Backyard garden], 16
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Close-up of back wall of house], 17
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas behind NBC microphones, dog on desk], 18
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast behind CBS microphone], 19
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast from behind his desk], 20
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas behind a desk with another man presenting a broadcast], 21
  - Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation], circa 1973; 5 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas sitting between two natives with painted faces], 1
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. on a page of a book. "Techniques of Magnetic Recording"], 3
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Close-up of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. holding a map in front of the Potala Palace], 4
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Article from The New Yorker. "Talk of the Town"], 5
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Quaker Hill Chapel], 6
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Quaker Hill Chapel], 7
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Inside of church], 8
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas holding a plaque next to another man], 9
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of land], 10
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lake in front of house], 11
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Frances Ryan Thomas in garden], 12
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Flower garden], 13
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Frances Ryan Thomas looking up at American flag], 14
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in golf cart], 15
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Road], 16
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Road], 17
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Road], 18
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: House on golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: House on golf course], 20
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course during the autumn], 21
  - Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation], circa 1973; 6 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: House on golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: House on golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lake in front of house on golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lake on golf course], 4
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 6
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas golfing, Frances Ryan Thomas and another woman sitting in red golf cart], 7
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 9
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 10
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Picnic tables set up on golf course by lake], 11
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on the patio with three others standing behind them], 12
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: People golfing on golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lake on golf course], 15
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas putting the golf ball], 16
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Road], 17
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf cart on course], 18
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: People golfing on golf course], 20
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 21
  - Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation], circa 1973; 7 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: People golfing on golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course during autumn], 3
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course during autumn], 4
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course during autumn], 5
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: People on golf course], 6
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of land], 7
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of land], 8
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of golf course], 9
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of golf course], 10
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Aerial view of golf course], 11
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas in golf cart with his dog], 12
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lake on golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Map of golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lake on golf course], 15
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas in red golf cart with his dog], 16
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: House on golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Indoor pool], 18
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas looking though golf clubs], 19
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Hammersley Hill Golf Club golf scorecard], 20
  - Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation], circa 1973; 8 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas talking with two other men], 1
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas sitting in a golf cart with a man, and another man standing beside them], 2
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Group of men with golf clubs, Lowell Thomas at center], 3
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Group of men together for a picture, Lowell Thomas at far left], 4
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Two men sitting in golf cart, Lowell Thomas and another man standing beside them], 5
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas and another man standing together], 6
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas and a group of men in a golf cart], 7
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas linking arms with a man, another man standing next to them], 8
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Group of men together for a picture, Lowell Thomas in the back at right], 9
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Group of men together for a picture, Lowell Thomas second from right], 10
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Three men standing together with Lowell Thomas standing at the right], 11
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Picture of man golfing with a letter from Richard Nixon about the Hammersley Hill Golf Club], 12
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas with another man in a golf cart], 13
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas with another man in a golf cart], 14
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: View of river? and golf course], 15
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course], 16
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course in the winter], 17
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Golf course in the winter, People on skiis], 18
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: House on golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: Lowell Thomas with his dog in a red golf cart], 20
    - [Carousel number 28 [Quaker Hill slide presentation]: (Blacked out photo)], 21
  - Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1], 1972 February 15; 9 (Box 1589)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1] [: Lowell Thomas giving a speech], 1
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Map of Alaska], 2
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: City street], 3
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Small city, snowy mountains in background], 4
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: People hiking on a snowy mountain], 5
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Large snowy mountain in the background], 6
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: River running by mountains], 7
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Factory?], 8
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Factory?], 9
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Aerial view of town, mountains in the distance, ocean?], 10
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Buildign in the distance], 11
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Men cutting trees], 12
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Flying in an airplane], 13
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Book page with a photo of a man], 14
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Woman with her arms around two children, smiling], 15
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Close-up of two children in Alaska], 16
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Boat on water, snowcapped mountains in the background], 17
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Boy with a rope around a reindeer, two other people wearing fur coats], 18
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Students sitting in a classroom], 19
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Side of a white house], 20
  - Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1], 1972 February 15; 10 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Factory?], 1
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Pipes], 2
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Book with a man's photo on page, Captioned "Hudson (?)"], 3
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Forrest], 4
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Sign that says "University of Denver (Colorado Seminary) Founded in 1864"], 5
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Sign that reads "Alaska Methodist University 1959"], 6
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Map of Alaska, showing its size], 7
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Building], 8
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Street], 9
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Road], 10
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Building], 11
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Building], 12
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Lowell Thomas speaking at podium], 13
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Woman teaching a class of younger kids], 14
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Man at top of mountain], 15
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Snowy road], 16
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: People walking on sidewalk by a building], 17
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: People skiing], 18
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Building], 19
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Person at blackboard], 20
  - Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1] [Items 1-3] Carousel number 30 [Items 4-20], 1972 February 15; 11 (Box 1589)
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Building with a view of mountains], 1
    - [Carousel number 29 [Alaska Methodist University, part 1]: Man working with controls], 2
    - Beginning of Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2] [: Street lined with streetlights], 3
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Snowy campus], 4
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Mountains and ocean?], 5
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Road, mountains in the background], 6
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: City, mountains in background], 7
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Snow covered pine trees and mountains], 8
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Mountain], 9
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Creek], 10
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: City located near mountain], 11
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Crane], 12
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Man holding a crab in each hand], 13
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Woman holding food in her hand at a store], 14
    - [Carousel number 30 [Alaska Methodist University, part 2]: Farm], 15